(Sheldon:)Okay.
As my future neighbor,
(Sheldon:)I'd like you to have a key.
(Sheldon:)Initial here to acknowledge
you received it.
(Penny:)I'm proud of you.
You're taking this really well.
(Sheldon:)Well, it's not like I'm never
going to see you two again.
(Sheldon:)Which brings us to
article 23 subsection C...
(Sheldon:)please check here
to reserve your spot
(Sheldon:)at the ten year
roommate reunion.
(Leonard:)Do I really have to do that now?
(Sheldon:)No, but if you want chicken
(Sheldon:)and get stuck with the fish,
that's on you.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and lastly,
(Sheldon:)please initial here to confirm
(Sheldon:)that ownership
of the living room couch
(Sheldon:)is hereby transferred to me
(Sheldon:)in perpetuity
all throughout the universe
(Sheldon:)and all alternate universes
(Sheldon:)except for those universes
where owning a couch
(Sheldon:)is forbidden by the hive queen.
(Sheldon:)In which case,
all glory to the hive queen.
(Sheldon:)All right,
now all that's left